sendmehits.com 2011-10-07

# SendMeHits.com - Free Traffic Exchange

### SendMeHits / Privacy Policy and Terms

Please read this Privacy Policy very carefully before using this site. The website you have entered is owned and operated by sendmehits.com. We are committed to protecting your privacy. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you about the publisher's practices relating to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information that may be provided to us during the registration process. This privacy policy also tells you what to do if you do not want your personal information collected and how you can change or delete information you have already provided to us. By using this website, you also agree with the following terms of service.

**What Personal Information We Collect and How We Use It**

Among other reasons, the publisher collects and retains information for the purposes of conducting market research, promotional activities, contests, surveys and advertisement mailings.

Personal information collected by the publisher are:  

  * contact information (full name, date of birth, gender, mailing address, and e-mail address); 

The publisher uses your personal information for the following purposes:

  * to develop and maintain our relationship with you and to communicate with you; 

  * to address your inquiries or respond appropriately; 

  * to develop and improve our products, services and websites and to advise you about new products and services from our websites and/or sponsors that may be of interest to you; 

  * to inform you of promotional events; 

  * to subscribe to newsletters, advertisement mailings and/or to conduct market research and surveys. 

  * to protect our business interests and the interests of our consumers, and to generally meet requirements imposed by law.

**When We Disclose Your Personal Information**

Except with your consent, we will not sell, share, license, trade or rent your personal information to others outside of the publisher's network of websites and related services. The publisher may disclose it's members' general information such as, but not limited to Age, Gender, Location to third parties, such as suppliers, advertising or promotional agencies, engaged to assist us in providing services to you or to carry out one or more of the purposes described above. We protect your personal information with appropriate security measures, and we require our suppliers, advertising and promotional agencies to do the same.

The publisher reserves the right to co-operate fully with local, provincial/state and federal officials in any investigation relating to any personal information (including private electronic communications transmitted on any the publisher websites) or any purported unlawful activities.

**Knowledge and Consent**

The publisher collects personal information only when you voluntarily provide it. If you don't want us to have access to your personal information, please do not provide it while using our sites. You may withdraw consent by using the appropriate link contained in all our mailings to unsubscribe from our mailing list.

**Cookies & IP Adresses**

The publisher does use session cookies on its network of websites to appropriately credit your account with playTokens when you refer others to our websites. When communicating with our website through a when referral and/or advertisement links, your IP is logged onto our server for authenticity purposes. Also our host is monitoring traffic mainly for keeping track of statistics and for network security reasons.

**How We Protect Your Personal Information**

The publisher makes all commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that personal information collected from you is protected against loss and unauthorized access. Access to your personal information is restricted to selected employees or representatives. In addition, The publisher employs generally accepted information security techniques, such as firewalls, access control procedures and cryptography, to protect personal information against loss and unauthorized access.

**Retention of Your Personal Information**

The publisher retains your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose for which it was collected, to comply with applicable laws and for the duration and extent of our business practice.

**Children's Privacy**

The publisher believes that it is very important to protect the privacy of children and encourages parents or guardians to spend time with their children to participate in and monitor their activities. The publisher does not intend to collect personal information from children, should we be aware that we have such information in our database it will promptly be deleted.

We also ensure that all advertising, sponsorship and promotional activity is not targeted at those under the age of 13. Please be aware that there may be links or content on an advertiser site that may contain mature content or that may be considered offensive to some. Please protect yourself as we are empowering you to take notice of all external site content. If an advertiser's site content is not appropriate and is considered offensive by you, please notify us and we will then investigate the matter.

**Links to Third Party Sites**

Our website may offer links to other websites which the publisher does not control. You should be aware that operators of linked websites may also collect your personal information (including information generated through the use of cookies) when you link to their websites. The publisher is not responsible for how such third parties collect, use or disclose your personal information, so it is important to familiarize yourself with their privacy policies before providing them with your personal information. These websites links are provided for your convenience and by including such websites The publisher is not implying that it endorses or recommends them. Same thing applies to promotional mailings we may send you on behalf of our advertisers.

Again, The publisher does not control advertiser content posted via our websites and does not guarantee the accuracy, integrity or quality of such content. You may be exposed to content that is offensive, indecent or objectionable to you the user. Under no circumstances will the publisher be liable in any way for any such content, including, but not limited to, any errors or omissions, or any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of the use of the content made available via all facets of communication with our websites and related services.

When you sign up and submit a request to participate in any one of our listed sweepstakes, contests, rewards or offers of the kind, you are giving expressed consent to that advertiser to contact you and utilize personal information that you have provided upon signup. This is the nature of any such offers; for the advertiser to be able to send information to you pertaining to their products and services. Please always read the advertiser's privacy policy before you join their sweepstakes or contests/offers. Protect yourself and act responsibly: read the terms and/or privacy policy governing subscription to any offers site and take notice of how your data will be utilized before entering them.

All offers on the pulisher's websites may require some kind of user participation. The publisher shall not be held responsible for any fulfilment requirements by any offering site nor the actual fulfilment of the offer itself. Visitors agree that the publisher shall not incur any liability for any defect, loss or fault caused, whether directly or indirectly, by any offer listed on the Publisher's websites.  

**Third Party Advertising**

The publisher may use third-party advertising companies and behavioral advertising networks to serve ads to you on their behalf when you visit our website(s). These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

**Contact Us**

We appreciate any customer feedback. If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at: [ customerservice@sendmehits.com](mailto:customerservice@sendmehits.com).

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, without prior notice. Depending upon the nature of these changes, you will be contacted, notified of these changes and will be asked to express affirmative consent. If you don't accept the changes to this privacy policy, you must unsubscribe from our list using the means described above and quit using our websites services. Your continued use of the publisher's websites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept these changes.

**Your Acceptance of These Terms** By using the publisher's websites, you signify your acceptance of the publisher Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our website or sign up for membership. If for any reason you do not agree with any of the changes whole in part, you must stop using the publisher's websites and terminate your membership using the unsubscribe link provided in our mailings for your convenience.

**Termination** The publisher reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to accept or reject any current member or any membership application for any reason, or for no reason, whatsoever.

Last updated: October 14th, 2010
